[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[theme music playing]
A LOVE OTHER THAN YOURS
[theme music concludes]
ALL PERSONS, LOCATIONS, RELIGIONS,
INCIDENTS, AND ORGANIZATIONS IN THIS DRAMA
ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS HAVE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER PARENTAL SUPERVISION
SCENES INVOLVING ANIMALS WERE FILMED
SAFELY WITH EXPERT ADVICE AND COOPERATION
YEONHWARU
[indistinct chatter]
[soft instrumental music playing
over speakers]
[swallows, sighs]
[door opens]
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
Question.
This is my first time here.
What do you recommend?
[sighs]
Hmm, boo-boo?
I'm not in a great mood today,
so I came in myself to have a drink.
And now some guy's talking to me.
Hmm?
Just ignore him and he'll get the clue?
-[chuckles softly]
-Okay.
[Namgung] Hey, Sang-hun.
Why are there
so many self-absorbed people lately?
I just wanted to have a drink.
It's my first time in this place,
so I asked for a recommendation.
And now some girl is under the impression
that I'm making a move on her,
which isn't the case. [laughs]
Talk about a grand delusion.
It's not fair I got rejected
before I even tried.
But you know what?
She's not even my type, really.
I doubt she knows that.
[gasps softly] Uh…
[passionate guitar music playing]
[both breathing heavily]
-[objects clattering]
-[panting]
We never introduced ourselves.
I'd go to a coffee shop
if I wanted to talk, don't you think?
-Has anyone told you you're a bit strange?
-Hmm, I bet the same goes for you.
Not really.
-Usually they tell me I'm a great kisser.
-[gasps]
[both panting, smooching]
Who told you that?
That you're a good kisser?
Does that really matter?
But you're not.
Kissing is all about
give and take, you know?
Oh, I thought you liked it rough.
Okay, got it.
I can be good at the give and take.
You know, let's stop.
Okay, I clearly said, "Let's stop."
[sighs]
Do you feel bad for your boyfriend?
Not at all.
I just think you're not as good
as you think you are.
-Not funny.
-Get off.
[music fades]
Ah, jeez.
[inhales deeply, sighs]
[tender piano music playing]
You're such a mood killer.
It's been a while. I was having fun.
-Ah!
-[smacks lips]
Hey!
[Mi-do]  Namgung and I
first met when we were seven.
[tender piano music continues]
-[sighs]
-[spits]
-[groans]
-[laughs]
[both laughing]
[Mi-do]  We've seen each other
at our absolute worst
more times than I can count.
[young Yeong-do]
"Do you know what solitude is?"
-[both laugh]
-"I watched a movie called  Taxi Driver
that taught me what it was."
"I was nine at the time…" [gasps]
[young Mi-do grunts]
[Mi-do]  We went through
our turbulent teens together.
[students shouting, laughing]
-[groans] What is it? Why did you hit me?
-[students gasping, murmuring]
-[young Mi-do] I'm really sorry.
-Listen, man, I'm sorry.
[whispers] What the hell?
-[gasps]
-[chuckles]
[Mi-do]  We stayed friends
for a very long time.
But then when we turned 26,
we started dating.
And before we knew it,
ten years had gone by.
It's not like this place is big.
Mi-do, you're literally two steps away
from the washing machine.
[indistinct chatter over video]
You never clean up.
[sighs]
Honestly, Mi-do, you only have one mouth.
-[cups clinking]
-Four cups, really?
I can't live like this.
[man over video]  Authorities
are monitoring a major storm system
moving through several regions,
bringing heavy rain and strong winds.
[sighs]
Hey, I asked you to crush the cans.
What's with this woman?
[man]
The storm arrived earlier than expected.
Some communities were caught off-guard.
-Emergency crews have been called.
-[water running]
[man]  They're working through
the evening to clear flooded roads
and assist the residents
in several affected areas,
according to the official report.
-Have there been any reports of injuries?
-[music fades]
-[grunts softly]
-[man]  And what can people expect
in the next few hours?
Forecasters say the worst of the weather
could continue through the night.
Residents of low-lying areas
-are being urged to stayed indoors.
-[sighs]
Director Lee, why are you
in such a bad mood lately?
[man]  Officials are also warning drivers
not to attempt to cross flooded roads.
One, production was delayed by two months.
Two, you went to the edit room,
watched the footage,
and Song Hae-na's acting's terrible.
Three, the producers keep
rejecting your music director.
[man continues speaking indistinctly
over video]
Four, I haven't kissed you.
[scoffs]
[chuckles] I knew it was four.
Or five.
I missed out on our shrimp toast
because you got home late.
[man]  Are schools expected
to remain open tomorrow?
Any communication about this
from the authorities?
[inhales sharply]
I can order chicken.
[man]  All right.
We'll continue to follow this story…
[gulps]
My treat? All combo.
Mustard, yogurt, garlic sauce.
-And double cheese sticks?
-Okay, deal.
Hmm. [chuckles]
You were against using CGI snow anyway.
Although it sucks that the producers
decided without telling you.
But it turned out fine, right?
Director Lee Mi-do
is known for mise-en-scène.
Just do your thing and kill it.
[man continues speaking indistinctly
over video]
Do you think I should just end it?
Mm. Go ahead.
[clicks tongue]
-[gentle guitar music playing]
-[vocalist singing in Korean]
1. WILL TEN YEARS TOGETHER
END IN MARRIAGE OR A BREAKUP?
NAMGUNG-TUSH
[cell phone vibrating]
[groans]
[groans] Wakey, wakey.
[groans] I love you, sweetie. Ciao, ciao.
I love you, sweetie. Ciao.
Huh.
[yawns]
[keypad beeping]
[coughs]
[vocalist continues singing in Korean]
-Hey! [sighs]
-[shower running]
SWEET DELIGHT FROM GOOD INGREDIENTS
[Hae-na over video]  Guess what?
Today I'm gonna show you
the set of the movie  No Heart.
-[breathes deeply]
-[Yeong-rae]  Hae-na?
[Hae-na]  Look, the director!
Huh? Didn't you tell her
no personal filming?
I told the manager since the beginning,
but I'm sorry, I'll go ahead
and tell them again.
-[sighs]
-[Mi-do]  Because of the genre,
even a prop can be a spoiler,
so personal filming
by staff and crew isn't allowed.
Get the video you just took cleared
by production first.
[Hae-na]  The director seems a little mad.
Now I need to make sure it gets cleared
so I can upload it for you.
CLEARED!
I'M SO HAPPY TO SHOW YOU
A GLIMPSE OF THE SET!
[vocalist continues singing in Korean]
DIRECTORS CAN'T BE SO AUTHORITARIAN
SHE DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THAT
DID YOU SEE HER EYES?
[commenter 1]  She directed the indie film
After Spring Comes Summer,
-the one starring Gong Ji-Seok.
-[music concludes]
[Namgung]  After Spring Comes Winter.
[commenter 2]  Didn't she win an award
before Bong Joon-ho?
[Namgung]  In 2018,
she won at Florence Shorts,
the first Asian woman
to ever achieve that.
[commenter 3]
The director looks really young,
even younger than Song Hae-na.
-Uh, no, I don't think so.
-[hums] Ah, jeez.
[gasps] Please, wait, boss, wait.
Listen to me, please. Sir.
-[hesitates]
-Uh…
I almost broke my back hauling those bags.
Take responsibility.
[laughs] Take responsibility?
What does that have to do with me?
Uh, wait, sir. I was wiping down
the conveyor belt, and look.
And I got hurt.
I was washing trays,
and now my joints hurt.
It looks all right.
Really? What do you mean, sir?
Thirty minutes ago, I started feeling pain
in my carpal tunnel.
God, the pain was unbearable. [chuckles]
I know you're doing this
because your team
got the fourth
Hatguma Chips sample, right?
There's no difference at all.
I told you that.
Yes, there is. I notice.
[indistinct chatter]
Our batch was the only one
preceded by Hoho Bakchip.
They're milk-fat based,
so no matter how much I CIP,
there's cross-contamination.
[factory manager] So what?
The fifth batch of Hoho Bakchip
is also scheduled before.
[sighs] You want me to change it?
It's hard to change schedules at year-end.
You know what I think? You think I'm weak.
That's why you're acting
so confident, right?
Not at all. I'm just saving up your debt.
-[inhales deeply, sighs]
-[bright quirky music playing]
I can buy you a Celint 18-year-old scotch
-like Assistant Manager Shin.
-[scoffs]
[Namgung] But I wonder
if I really have to go that far.
-And honestly, I don't want to.
-[scoffs]
-Listen, I hate being pathetic.
-[sighs]
Although, I'm confident in using my body.
What are you talking about?
Tell me, why'd you do all that?
-Who asked you to volunteer?
-Oh, no.
[gasps]
Where did it go?
Huh? I'm sure it was here, or not.
-What?
-I guess I left it at home.
-Missing something? What?
-Have you seen it?
Your conscience, manager.
Jeez, you're such a…
If you work me to the bone for a week,
you should be able
to calculate the price properly.
-Anyway, using my hourly wage…
-[scoffs]
…calculated for my base salary,
three hours a day, four on Thursday,
and I came after work.
-[scoffs]
-If you multiply that by seven… [gasps]
I was even more expensive
than a Celint 18-year-old scotch.
That's 370,000 won.
-[factory manager sighs]
-[gasps] My God, that's a lot, huh?
[factory manager sighs]
HUNMIN CONFECTIONERY
[bright quirky music continues]
[sighs]
[intriguing musical sting]
[groans, sighs]
[smooching sound effect]
How long is this gonna go on?
-Until you finally give in.
-[inhales deeply]
The executives already fixed it.
How can we change it?
-Will you take responsibility if it fails?
-That's your job, isn't it?
You get paid two million more than me.
Seriously? Why?
-Ah, shut it.
-[sighs]
-[sighs] Okay, fine.
-[music fades]
I admit there's a slight difference
in sweetness,
but the internal survey shows
similar responses overall,
from the first to fourth batch.
So statistically,
there's no real difference.
These are the internal survey comments
for Hatguma Chips.
Take a look. Here.
[groans]
HATGUMA CHIPS
INTERNAL SURVEY RESULTS
[Su-a]  There isn't sweet potato flavor.
Aftertaste is the worst.
At this rate,
it'll flop without even launching.
-What's this?
-[Su-a]  My condolences.
Did you write this?
It's exactly what you just said.
I know, right? I even thought,
"Huh? Did I sabotage this while drunk?"
[whimsical instrumental music playing]
I think you forgot this
because you're aging, sir.
Something similar happened
with Hot Choco Chips.
Guess who noticed
the steam input error back then?
I hate to say this myself,
but I caught it.
[Sang-hun] Holy moly.
So that's the Hot Choco Chips
origin story?
It's an honor to hear it.
I can't believe it.
-Stop it.
-[whip cracking sound effect]
[sighs] I worked all week
to change the factory schedule.
[scoffs] Jeez, all for nothing.
Okay. November, first week.
No more delays.
-[groans] Hey, get off! [grunts]
-[cell phone vibrating]
Just a minute.
YEONHUI-DONG TWIN FISTS
-[Ho-sik] Get back to work. Right now.
-I'll be right back.
-Oh, what a pain.
-[music concludes]
QUEENS HAIR SALON
-[Namgung] Oh, looks delicious.
-[Mi-do] Oh, it's so good.
[cutlery clinking]
[Namgung slurps]
[Mi-do] So good.
-[Namgung chews, sighs] Oh, spinach.
-[Mi-do] Mm.
Eat your spinach.
[both munching]
You two.
-[Mi-do sighs]
-Decide right now.
Are you tying the knot or calling it off?
You gotta choose.
[Yeong-do scoffs] Uh, Mom, are you crazy?
He has a great salary,
full-time corporate job,
and solid gains.
Why would Namgung settle for someone
who doesn't even get insurance?
-Does that make sense?
-Mom, listen.
Namgung's happiness
is just as important as--
-[grunts]
-[both groan]
It's true, Mom!
[Yeong-do sighs]
[sighs]
Listen… quit playing dumb,
you two. [sighs]
[quirky piano music playing]
Um, Gang Dong-won is almost in.
We have Chinese investors, too.
29-YEAR-OLD LEE MI-DO
It's happening faster than I thought.
Anyway, you just keep looking
for an apartment.
[munches]
[gasps] Gong Yoo is gonna do it!
"Drama or movie?" That was the question.
30-YEAR-OLD LEE MI-DO
He'll make a decision soon,
and we'll sign next week.
He's in.
Keep looking for that apartment, honey.
[gasps] He didn't sign!
Do you think I wanted this?
The production company suddenly folded.
32-YEAR-OLD LEE MI-DO
Whatever.
We're shaking off the bad luck. [gasps]
I'm serious, okay? Listen closely.
That apartment is going to be ours.
[breathes heavily]
33-YEAR-OLD LEE MI-DO
So, the investors' response
isn't bad, you know?
I'm sure that they are…
I know it's not closed yet,
but we'll keep looking
for that apart-- Ah!
-[music fades]
-Oh, come on. There's no rush.
[sword drawing sound effect]
[hesitates]
-Good point. You better listen.
-[whimsical guitar music playing]
Your mom says that out of love,
-we should…
-[sword drawing sound effect]
-Hey, I'm with you. Just ignore it.
-[sighs]
[chuckles softly] Here.
Ma'am, you saw all the articles
about Mi-do's movie, right?
This time it's for real.
I know it. [grunts]
Oh, Mom, I saw some articles, too.
Song Hae-na posted it online.
-Oh.
-[Wan-do] Yeah.
Although filming a movie
doesn't mean it'll get finished.
Ma, so many movies
these days never actually come out.
And that's a shame bec…
[gulps]
Anyway, I'm sure it's real this time.
Don't stress out Lee Mi-do.
You may look down on her,
but out there, she's respected.
Enough.
You two promised, right?
That you'd get married
once she becomes a director?
This is not a joke.
Six months.
-[sighs]
-Uh…
There's a little issue,
'cause Mi-do's filming got delayed
because of the snowy mountain
and the process of editing--
-[music concludes]
-If you keep overthinking it,
you'll never do it.
Either it works or you make it work.
But stop making excuses.
Get married or break up.
-[slams spoon]
-[sighs]
Look at you. I just said what I thought,
but you can't handle it.
That temper of yours.
Antacid?
Does your tummy hurt? You okay?
Hey, are you…
Not at all.
You shouldn't take any medicine.
You never know.
Didn't you hear, Mom? I said no.
How can you be so sure, huh?
It never hurts to be careful.
We haven't had sex in six months.
[splutters, coughs]
[whimsical guitar music playing]
[clears throat]
Hey, why would you say
that in front of your mom?
-Are you out of your mind or what?
-[music concludes]
If I hadn't, we'd be arguing over Guam
or Cebu for our honeymoon by now.
You're welcome, okay?
You don't say?
God, you oversharing
is just what I needed.
-Well, I wasn't lying, was I?
-Hey, that's not…
We've both been busy lately, so…
[inhales sharply]
That long already?
-Two, and then--
-[gasps] Stop counting, okay?
[sighs] Well, if you say so.
[sighs]
I told you not to go, didn't I?
My mom's never gonna let this go.
I really think that she's just doing that
because she's worried about you.
It's just delayed because of your film.
We've talked about the wedding.
What do you mean?
You actually want to tie the knot?
Mm. Of course I do.
You don't?
[car horn blares, fades]
It's not that I don't want to.
I'm just scared.
[sighs] Getting married…
[sighs]
…it's ending the second act of life
and entering the third act,
but I feel like my second act
isn't even done yet.
I mean, sure,
I'm shooting a movie right now.
I don't know how it'll turn out.
[sighs]
I know what I'm like.
I'm selfish and I only care about myself.
And I know if I marry you,
the comfort you give me
would be enough for me to settle.
I'll stop writing
and live off you like a leech.
But I can't do that.
A nightmare, that's what that sounds like.
So I was just a leech to you then, huh?
Hey!
That's the thing.
That's not being a leech.
Call it reliance, coexistence, or care.
I didn't mean…
Drink this. Your tummy hurts.
I have leftover abalone. Do you want it?
You were just picking
at your food earlier.
I don't want that. Make fried rice.
Your tummy hurts. Just eat this.
Do you remember that day?
In ninth grade during summer break?
[gentle piano music playing]
[pants]
EMERGENCY ROOM
This way. This way.
[Namgung]  I was running
with you on my back.
And you didn't feel heavy at all.
[doctor] Lee Mi-do! Lee Mi-do!
-Run a blood test.
-[nurse] Yes, doctor.
I'll take your temperature.
[Namgung]  And I found out later…
I carried you six miles
in just 30 minutes.
So don't say anything about being a leech.
When you're clinging to my back…
that's when I'm strongest.
You're like… [inhales sharply]
…a booster.
You keep me moving forward.
My movie might flop this time.
-Is that okay?
-Yeah.
Even if breathing
while holding your back, is that…
-Mm-hmm. That's fine.
-And if I kill someone?
Hey.
-I said I'd do anything for you, but…
-Answer me.
Well…
first I'd curse you out.
Really bad.
Then I'd bring you stuff in jail.
[chuckles softly]
[knife chopping]
[gasps] The carrots.
I hate the crunch.
Chop them smaller, okay?
Yeah, yeah.
[Namgung] Why are you awake?
Namgung.
Is it really okay if my movie fails?
[inhales deeply]
Of course.
It's totally fine.
Just do your best with no regrets.
Just do that.
[music concludes]
[shower running]
[actor moaning]
[moaning continues in higher pitch]
-[walkie-talkie beeps]
-Cut. Let's take a short break.
-[crew member 1] We're taking a break.
-[crew members sighing]
[indistinct chatter]
24 HOURS IS NEVER ENOUGH
[inhales deeply, sighs]
Uh, I'm really sorry.
This kind of movie is a first for me.
[breathes shakily]
Maybe you don't know this, but I debuted
in Director Hwang Sun-gi's  Manifesto.
I was a rising star in Chungmuro.
I appeared in a lot of dramas.
I'm talking too much.
-[sighs]
-My guess is D flat or E?
-What?
-Ah, ah…
[in higher pitch] …ah.
Uh-huh. It's the pitch. Can you do that?
-[lowering pitch] Ah, ah, ah.
-Huh.
If the man's moans are higher pitched
than the woman's,
-it doesn't work, right?
-Ah, ah. Huh.
Okay, in five minutes,
we'll resume shooting.
[crew member 2] Copy that.
[dramatic classical music playing
over speakers]
[Yeon-ju] The CEO also feels bad
about this whole situation.
Articles of your departure
will go out once we settle.
Oh, as for your replacement,
we're trying to find someone whose style
matches your creative approach.
Because of the on-location
snow scene shoot,
we have to wait a month anyway,
so there's no rush.
Tell me, do you have questions?
I've watched for 30 minutes,
and there are four low angle shots.
-About time.
-[actor]  Hey, why are you here?
[Yeon-ju] That's because Song Hae-na
needed time
to get her nose surgery corrected.
-[scoffs]
-[actor]  What do you mean?
-[music fades]
-Anyway, honestly,
I didn't realize you were such
a hard worker until now.
It hasn't even been two weeks
since you left the film,
and you're already on your next project.
It's extraordinary.
Well… [sighs]
…I've got a messy court battle
coming up soon, and I can't afford it.
Mm-hmm.
[Hae-na over TV]
I don't know why I can't forget you.
Is there something else?
We all want to thank you
for everything you've done, ma'am.
Now I won't talk as a producer.
Listen to me
as a high school friend, okay?
-We're friends?
-As a classmate, then.
I'm trying to be kind,
so please listen closely.
Try that for just a second.
[sighs]
A lawyer will call you this week
about the settlement.
-Don't try to go to court. Just sign it.
-No.
It'll be a messy fight
if you decide to take it to court.
Do you want to turn this into a bloodbath?
That's why I do it, you know?
-[pensive music playing]
-Everything is a mess now.
I'm as low as it gets,
and that won't change a thing.
[Yeon-ju sighs]
[sighs]
Thanks for the advice. Not that it helped.
[water burbling]
TWO WEEKS AGO
[music fades]
Hey, like we prepped,
we need some tracking shots.
Director, I have a message
from Song Hae-na
saying she can't film today.
And why?
-Because of a private brand event today.
-[sighs]
[Yeong-rae] Her manager forgot about it.
[sighs] I can't.
[upbeat instrumental music playing]
[grunts] What? What? What is it?
[manager] Director, wait right there.
Hold on, please.
Allison Matin D Series.
Patek Philippe, Louis Vuitton suit.
Cheongdam Louvacity wine bar.
Height between 5'11" and six feet.
It was Wednesday, October 14th.
That's when Song Hae-na said
she couldn't film 'cause she was sick.
Should I go on?
Uh…
[music intensifies]
I told the assistant director about this.
My photo call got moved up.
Out of 22 shoots,
you haven't shown up for seven.
I'm sorry.
You change everything on a whim.
Lines, the shot list,
even the storyboards.
I try to be understanding
since you're a rookie,
but when there are inconsistencies
between the call sheet and the shoot,
-it throws everyone off.
-[breathes deeply]
I figured you needed more time
to avoid all the confusion,
but I held back
and didn't talk to you about it.
I thought it'd put you on the spot.
I was being considerate,
but it caused confusion on your side.
You're saying that it's my fault then?
That's what happens
when you work with an amateur.
Honestly, I should have known better.
The wire set up at the tank
looked quite unsafe earlier.
How can I work in an unsafe set?
Should I risk my life for a single shoot?
The main wire has backup. It's double-set.
We went as far as getting autobraking gear
to maintain tension during depth shifts.
We calculated your weight
to a 0.1 pound margin
and prepared the harness.
Water temp is 75 degrees.
Tank pressure is set.
Two safety divers are also on standby.
All good?
-Block them.
-[all clamoring]
[grunts]
Everyone get ready.
We shoot in five minutes.
[Yeong-rae] I said you can't go in.
-Please calm down while we're shooting.
-[overlapping chatter]
[music crescendos, fades]
Are you out of your mind?
I'm not letting this go.
I know you're doing this on purpose.
[breathes deeply]
Your lover. He's married, right?
Strange how he was more careful
than an actress.
He even switched cars twice on the way.
Your absences always matched
to his schedule.
Always on a Monday.
Every single time you've claimed
to be sick and in terrible shape.
Also, you were hysterical.
-Are you stalking me? Seriously?
-Yeah.
And this is blackmail, okay?
[low somber music playing]
You might see this as just a passing film,
but for me, not the case.
'Cause this is my one shot.
I'm working like my life
depends on this show.
My life at risk here.
If you don't want your life ruined
over dating a married man,
we better start working together.
'Cause I'm not sure what I might do.
-Okay, let's get Hae-na in a harness.
-[crew member] Yes, ma'am.
[harness jangling]
-Get it ready for her safety.
-[crew member] Copy that.
[Hae-na] Director.
[music intensifies]
If you're really that scared
of your life coming to an end,
then I should end it for you.
Goodbye, Madam Director.
-[gasps]
-[crew members screaming, shouting]
[gasps]
[indistinct murmuring]
[breathes shakily]
[breathes deeply]
[sighs]
[music concludes]
[dogs barking in distance]
[cell phone vibrates]
[Namgung]  Yeong-do says
we're out of beer, so hurry.
Where are you? I'll pick you up.
[funky music playing over cell phone]
This is what
it's all about, guys! [screams]
You freaked me out!
[gasps]
-What?
-[sighs]
-[snorts]
-[music concludes]
The street lighting is terrible.
Top-down lighting ruins everything.
I saw some of your videos.
You've got a good eye.
The thing you have is no taste.
Whatever. It's just a hobby.
-I'll probably quit after a few.
-[chuckles softly]
You got your lying abilities from your mom
and your incompetence from your dad.
That's on you.
Everyone's trashing me
saying I take after you.
Oh, yeah, right.
Auntie, were you a bully in kindergarten?
[Yeong-do over video]  Look, don't forget.
Mi-do got freaking kicked out
of kindergarten.
-Twice, actually.
-Oh, jeez.
Yeah?
You do know she walks around
with trash in her pockets, right?
It's actually fun taking it all out.
Oh, and she wore the same socks
for three days.
-I saw it. It's true. You saw it too?
-[Namgung laughs]  She still does that.
But just a few times,
and she never goes past four days.
-And you're okay with that?
-[bright whimsical music playing]
You still want to marry her, Namgung?
[Wan-do] Hey, hey, hey. Give it up.
We've already listed 72 of her flaws,
but he's still sure.
That's true love.
[sighs]
Hey, if you're gonna marry her,
you'd be better off becoming a monk.
[Namgung]  Don't say things
like that in front of her.
She acts tough, but she really gets hurt.
-But she brings it on herself.
-Careful now.
[sighs] Hey, each time you see Mi-do,
does your heart still flutter?
Does it go thump, thump, pitter-patter?
Hmm.
[music concludes]
Mm-hmm. It still flutters.
I miss her when she's not around,
and I feel empty without her.
Even if we're together 24/7,
time flies by. I never get sick of her.
-Shocking, right? I'm shocked as well.
-[tender piano music playing]
[Namgung sighs over video]
HUNMIN CONFECTIONERY
[music concludes]
[sighs]
Sir…
how could you stab me
in the back like this? [scoffs]
Why would you even do that?
We already agreed
to postpone the schedule.
One, you backed off asking
General Manager Kang for a delay.
Two, you backed off from meeting
the year-end release timeline.
Three, next month TF Snack Teams One
and Five are dropping their products.
So please tell me, what's the reason?
-That way I can--
-[Su-a] Or four.
He backed off because the sample
from Snack Team Five was high quality.
Uh…
I'm sorry.
You're not my manager.
[chuckles awkwardly]
I apologize.
Team Five's sample
cannot be that excellent.
The sample that came out yesterday is.
-Yesterday?
-I got to taste it.
We share a research team.
The previous version lacked
a sweet and salty balance,
but they really improved it.
Uh, the aftertaste is good
and has a bold flavor.
I bet their survey results
will beat your team's, too.
Hmm.
You wrote "my condolences," did you?
Snack Team Four, Park Su-a.
TF Snack Team Three,
Assistant Manager Namgung Ho.
The reason the fourth sample had issues…
I know what it is.
Do you wanna know?
[automated voice speaking indistinctly
over screen]
WHEN THAT DAY COMES
[automated voice]  This summer,
one decision will change everything.
This summer, the past comes back.
[cell phone vibrating]
INCOMING CALL
[cell phone continues vibrating]
[soft music playing over speakers]
[Tae-seung] Nice to meet you.
I'm the attorney for Nobu Film.
Han Tae-seung, a pleasure.
[chuckles softly]
This is our draft of the settlement.
I thought it best to offer it first.
SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT
Take a look, and let me know if you have
any kind of questions or revisions.
[pensive instrumental music playing]
The directing fee won't be paid in full,
and a three percent copyright stake?
My client's aware
that you are the one at fault here,
so we ask for your understanding.
This is absurd. I can't.
[inhales deeply]
Because you forced the shoot,
Song Hae-na sustained
an injury during filming.
That situation left her suffering
from mental distress,
and she refused to finish the film.
So naturally, you're the one
who's responsible for all this.
[scoffs]
Anyone who heard you
would think she broke a leg.
That's not all. Don't forget your exit
caused bigger losses than expected,
including wages of more
than 40 crew members for two months.
The soundstage rental alone cost
over 300 million won.
What if I don't agree to this settlement,
and I don't sign?
I can't say for sure,
but maybe around next month,
an article titled,
"Lee Mi-do, director of the film  No Heart,
fired for incompetence,"
will probably be published.
But if you sign, it can change to,
"Director Lee Mi-do leaves  No Heart
due to health reason."
[chuckles]
That's a lot more flattering
than being fired.
Right?
But of course, the choice
is completely your call.
But sadly, we don't have much time left.
So I'll need your answer by next week
-at the latest.
-[knocking on door]
[door opens]
[music fades]
-What? What do you want?
-Sorry.
-I came in because you rang. Did you not?
-What?
I'm the one who rang.
I can order freely, right?
[sighs]
Hmm… [inhales sharply]
One bottle of your finest scotch,
also bring some fruit on the side.
-And ice and sparkling water.
-[waiter] Yes.
-I'll prepare that right away.
-[Mi-do] Mm.
I'll get the final settlement
to you next week.
You seem busy, so you can leave.
[sighs]
[scoffs]
[soft music playing over speakers]
Do you remember Chairman Choi's case
from last year?
Back then, the prosecution
also talked about intent,
but we got a no-charge disposition.
Just leave it all to me
-and go prepare for your next gig.
-[knocking on door]
Yeah?
[chuckles]
Shit. How many bottles
are we talking about here?
Two Monterio 21s, one 30-year,
and the first bottle of Ravelo.
-[upbeat pop music playing over speakers]
-[all shouting, cheering]
[shouting, cheering fades]
[dramatic music playing over speakers]
What would you like to do?
[sighs] Don't let them order anymore.
[waiter] Of course, sir.
She's a fucking lunatic.
[all sigh]
-[indistinct chatter over TV]
-[sighs]
Are you going
to sign the settlement, director?
Are you crazy? Why would she do that?
[Guk-jin] Still, this tyranny
from the production company
and the actor.
We need to just expose everything
to the world.
Hey, that's a terrible idea.
If this blows up,
it'll only make things harder for her.
[Jang-mi] Shut up for one second.
-You're way too loud.
-Guys, just stop.
All of you, stop reporting to my set.
That's why I called you.
I only hired you for a bit
because I was short on staff.
I wasn't keeping you.
My director friend
is filming something new,
and I asked him to hire the three of you.
Go do your damn best, okay?
Don't put me on the spot.
No, I don't want to.
I want to keep working with you, director.
Lee Guk-jin, stop the complaining.
If you have time for that,
go write a screenplay.
-Mm.
-Go, go, go. Let's go.
[whimsical instrumental music playing]
Huh? Hey, bae.
[breathes heavily]
[police officer] Now tell me,
how did you know they were there?
-[music concludes]
-They practically flaunted it online.
[police officer] So you saw the post
on her socials and went?
-Who threw the first punch?
-This jerk did.
-He came at me, no warning.
-She was cheating on me.
How could I not be mad about it?
I've already told you a thousand times,
that's not it,
-all right?
-Hey!
-Then what were you doing, huh?
-That's enough already.
It's all because of you.
Fired from your own movie
and shooting porn.
You should be ashamed.
Why use her as your staff
in a place like that?
Ruin your own life if you want to.
Shooting an adult film isn't embarrassing.
Your behavior right now is.
-[scoffs]
-And Jang-mi doesn't deserve this.
What? Don't speak to me like…
What are you doing?
[groans loudly]
-[sighs]
-[Jang-mi's boyfriend whimpers]
[sighs]
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
But I can explain. [breathes heavily]
I heard it all. No need to explain.
Looks like you
and Song Hae-na clashed again.
And you need money for a lawyer.
So you decided to go behind my back
and did an adult film.
-I'm sorry.
-Is Yeon-ju the PD?
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
They haven't found a director yet.
This is your last chance.
[sighs]
How will you face your mom
after this mess, huh?
How are you gonna
explain this to everyone?
How will you lie to yourself
and pretend you're okay?
You're not okay.
You need to understand that.
So it isn't okay if I fail?
It does matter.
Not to me. It does to you.
Don't you care about that?
Why would you let some random idiot
tell you you're ruining your life?
I made myself clear.
What did I tell you?
Do your best with no regrets.
But you will regret this. I know you will.
I'll handle it.
This is my job.
It's none of your business.
Then just stop doing things that worry me!
-[somber piano music playing]
-[scoffs]
Look where handling it got you.
This is the result.
How can I do nothing?
You should have told me first.
I could have helped you to--
I didn't want you to see it.
This side of me is too pathetic
for you to see.
[breathes heavily]
And I'm too ashamed of it.
[sighs]
So this is how it feels.
[breathes heavily]
[sighs]
[breathes deeply]
[door lock beeping]
Mi-do, listen.
[music concludes]
-I understand, let's--
-Let's end it, now.
-Wait, Mi-do…
-I need to end our relationship.
[sighs]
Look, I was wrong earlier.
I shouldn't have talked to you like that.
I was only thinking of myself. I get it.
When did it start?
You said I was your driving force
and compass. Tell me since when.
[poignant instrumental music playing]
[Namgung over video]
Hmm. I still get butterflies.
How is this possible?
It amazes me too.
I'd love to say that, but it's not true.
[Yeong-do]  Man, I thought it was true.
[Wan-do]  So you don't get
butterflies anymore?
[Namgung]  I've been with Mi-do
for ten years,
so it'd be weird if I still did.
To me, Mi-do is my reason
for staying loyal to a company.
She's my life's compass.
Whenever I think about quitting my job,
she's the force that keeps me going.
So I see her as the compass that keeps me
from straying off the right path.
I just have to get through
another 30 years.
[chuckles]  I want to grow old fast.
[sighs]
I'm a heavy burden to you.
It's too much to handle.
This is for the best.
[sighs] Listen, Mi-do.
It's not like that.
That's not really what I meant.
You know exactly how I feel, don't you?
I know the butterflies are gone.
You said so yourself.
Seeing me doesn't get
to you anymore, does it?
Does your heart race? It doesn't.
We've been together for ten years now.
That's normal, you know?
Namgung, do you know why
I wasn't a burden that day?
You loved me, so I wasn't happy.
So you've made up your mind, right?
So this is it, you're really ending us?
It's true.
We've changed, I know that.
Yet… everything we've been through
doesn't just go away.
It's not like we don't love each other.
I mean, everyone goes through that.
How can we stay passionate forever?
I will try harder.
Mi-do…
I think I've been neglecting you.
[poignant instrumental music continues]
So I'll try three times as hard, I swear.
Then I'll be three times heavier.
And I'll feel worse than I already do.
Namgung…
can't you see that…
your sense of responsibility,
obligation, and remorse…
highlight how pathetic I am?
And now I think I hate myself.
What?
You know… I have to be
so careful around you.
It's easy to confuse being careful
around someone with being considerate.
Being considered
makes me feel like I'm good.
But when I'm too careful around someone,
I feel pathetic.
And if I feel any more pathetic,
I'm afraid I'll lose it.
Mm.
That's why we should end all this.
So my love makes you feel pathetic?
[scoffs]
So you really want to break up with me?
[music concludes]
Mm.
You're completely sure then, is that it?
[sighs]
Last time I'll ask.
Think carefully.
Do you really want to end it?
Mm. I do.
Okay.
Fine. Good luck.
[door lock beeping]
[sobbing]
-[somber instrumental music playing]
-[vocalist singing in Korean]
[breathes deeply]
[sobbing]
[sighs]
LOVING YOU
WAS THE BEST THING I'VE EVER DONE
IT'S BEEN TEN YEARS,
BUT I'M STILL GETTING TO KNOW YOU
LET'S KEEP BEING US AND STAY TOGETHER
I LOVE YOU
[Mi-do]  Our time together
was as bright as the sun.
Our time together was so beautiful…
that nothing's changed.
It's still the same.
I fooled myself, and I fooled you.
[vocalist continues singing in Korean]
[Mi-do grunts softly]
[sighs, grunts]
But we both know something.
The love between us doesn't shine anymore.
The weight of our love is suffocating.
It's withered and pathetic.
[cell phone vibrating]
MY BABY
[Wan-do sighs]
-They picking up?
-Hmm.
-Are you for real?
-Mm.
-Did those two get into a fight?
-Ah, shit.
What do we do?
What do you mean? Everything's ready.
Try calling again.
TO THE ONE ALWAYS BY MY SIDE
[Wan-do] Ah, damn.
MI-DO, WILL YOU MARRY ME?
[vocalist continues singing in Korean]
[Mi-do sobbing]
[exhales heavily]
Just like that,
our ten-year relationship ended.
[groans softly]
[cell phone vibrating]
NAMGUNG-TUSH
[music concludes]
[Mi-do] Good morning.
Wakey, wakey.
[groans] I'm getting up.
I love you, sweetie. Ciao, ciao.
Hmm. I love you, sweetie. Ciao, ciao.
-[gasps]
-[upbeat rock music playing]
[Mi-do screams]
[screams]
[breathes heavily]
Oh!
[Namgung groans]
[music concludes]
[woman 1] Oh, it's snowing.
SHORT FILM SCREENING
[man] Whoa. So today
is the first snow in Seoul.
The weathermen called it.
DIRECTOR LEE MI-DO
LOOKING FORWARD TO YOUR NEXT FILM
WISHING YOU GOOD HEALTH
Excuse me. Did you see who wrote this?
Uh… [inhales sharply]
He just left a little while ago.
[Mi-do gasps]
[woman 2] Wait, Ms. Lee,
your interview starts soon.
Director Lee!
[panting]
AFTER SPRING COMES WINTER
[gasps]
[Yeong-do sighs]  He's going to Australia.
One of his classmates
is running a big Korean restaurant there.
He reached out
to go into business together.
He says he can never be friends with you.
He says he's tired of it.
He hates Korea because of you.
[breathes deeply]
[Yeong-do]
He'll come back once he's over you.
[sobs]
[tender piano music playing]
[sniffles, breathes deeply]
[announcer over PA]
The next buses arriving are in 12 minutes
and 45 minutes.
[breathes deeply]
[gasps]
[breathes heavily]
You were following me.
You should have followed me all the way.
[sighs]
Mi-do, you're something else.
If I don't come to you,
then you won't come to me.
You said you wouldn't be friends with me.
Yeah, I won't.
I won't.
You really are such a pain in the ass.
[sniffles]
But I'm pretty sure of what scares you.
Because I was terrified too.
Still… listen, Mi-do.
What you're scared of won't happen.
The whole dating and breaking up cliché…
it won't happen to us.
How can you be so sure?
'Cause I love you more than anything.
More than you can even imagine.
So much that it burns me inside.
I love you so much that it hurts.
[breathes deeply]
[music swells]
[music softens]
[music concludes]
[Mi-do]  That day,
we became more than friends,
-and the first snow fell in Seoul.
-[dramatic rock music playing]
[Mi-do]  After that,
our anniversary wasn't a date,
but the day
the first snow falls in Seoul.
We welcomed nine first snows together
and loved each other madly.
But before the tenth first snow,
we broke up.
[vocalist singing in Korean]
♪ I hear your voice in the quiet night ♪
[vocalist continues singing in Korean]
THANK YOU TO OH DONG-MIN
FOR HIS SPECIAL APPEARANCE
[Yeong-do sighs]
You're gonna apologize anyway.
Aren't you worried about Mi-do?
[Namgung]  Mi-do and I broke up.
You know that.
[Mi-do]  It could go either way.
-[Namgung]  Don't make excuses later.
-[Mi-do]  You too.
The Spicy SweeTato Chips
were really bad.
I smoke too.
I've smoked since high school.
Can I bum one?
[Mi-do]  I'll kill you
if you come here again.
[Tae-seung]  Since you want it so badly,
I'll see you in court.
[Namgung]  What is it this time?
-That's none of your business now.
-I don't want to care anymore.
[Mi-do]  Where did all that passion go?
Hmm? And the butterflies?
Where did they fly away to?
♪ But you fade away ♪
[music concludes]